gkrishan751@gmail.com +917550170911 Ambala, India 133201

Skills

- Design and development
- Requirements gathering
- Testing and deployment
- · Review of designs

Education And Training

08/2020

Bachelor Of Technology:

Electrical, Electronics And **Communications Engineering**

Chennai

Krishan Gopal

Summary

Knowledgeable and experienced Senior Software Engineer well-versed in OOP concepts and design patterns. Excellent API design, implementation and integration abilities paired with significant project leadership background. Exceptional success in delivering complex software development projects on time and within budget to exceed expectations.

Experience

SuprDaily By Swiggy - Senior Software Engineer

Bangalore, India 04/2022 - Current

11PM PICKING

- Lead the Product End To End i.e. from gathering product requirement, documented changes to delegate work among other team member
- As a part of 11PM picking we have completely change the way we handle the Customer Order at warehouse that help us to reduce the manpower, improve customer experience etc.
- Met with stakeholders, product teams and customers throughout system development lifecycle.

Packaging Suggestions

- As a part of Packaging Suggestions we had introduced the suggestion of packaging Material for packing of Customer Order Items
- Designed a system in such a way so that it can easily extensible for future changes
- Create/Run script to generate the packaging suggestion data before rolling out the feature on Production for better suggestion and adherence

Deliver Fresh

- As a part of **Deliver Fresh** Project we want to make sure that customer experience should be good with respect to the freshness of product
- Go through all the domains and figure out what are all the places we need to make changes
- Divide the project into milestones and delegate work among other team member
- Suggest the product design to reduce the cost of procurement of new assets

SuprDaily By Swiggy - Software Engineer

Bangalore, India 05/2021 - 04/2022

OYO - Software Engineer

Hyderabad, India 12/2019 - 05/2021

Accomplishments

• Awarded by Most valuable player Title for my continuous input and working on projects which is both time and business-critical for the company